♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He working at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worse we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ Crow ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(clanging)
(whirring)
- Oh now, what is this?
Oh, this is my second
grade piano recital.
Hey Gypsy, wake
up, check this out.
Oh, you actually get a feeling
for what it was like
to really be there.
- Oh yeah, this is
really interesting.
- Joel, these are fascinating.
Now who took these?
- Um, Uncle Roy.
- Oh yeah, the
guy with the mole.
- Right, exactly.
Gypsy, check this out.
- So cute.
- Hi everybody.
Welcome to the
satellite of love.
Well you can
probably tell by now
that Joel just transferred
all his old home movies
to video tape.
- You know what, I think this
is that picnic we took
up to Koshkonong Mounds.
- Koshkonong Mounds?
- I'm kind of worried
about Tom Servo.
- Oh, so watch what I do now.
Gypsy, check this out.
- You pulled his short's down!
(laughing)
Now that's funny.
Hey, are those
Minnie's kids there?
- No, that's Brent and Brenda.
They're Brian and
Bridgette's kids.
Minnie's kids are--
- Oh, Ray and Tony.
- Right, and Theresa.
- Oh yeah.
This is fascinating!
- Tommy, don't go in too far!
- Hey, look what I found.
Swing choir tape.
- Swing choir?
♪ The world is black,
the world is white ♪
(upbeat music)
- Alright, explain to me again
how this bulk eraser fell out
of the closet and on to
these home movie transfers
when the closet isn't
anywhere around here?
- Yeah, weird, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Ah, no matter, I've got
duplicates in my foot locker.
- Yeah, I know.
I found those.
- Oh Marilyn McCoo and Billy
Davis Junior are calling.
Crow.
- Ah Joel.
I wonder if you wouldn't
indulge me today.
Frank's been down a bit lately
and well, when the poor fellow's
not shuffling head
down through the lab,
he's locked himself in his room
watching old Misfits
of Science episodes.
So to pick him up I
thought I'd let him
do this week's
invention exchange.
Really put the spark back in.
- [Frank] Dr. F, I'm ready
for this week's invention.
- We're ready for you, Frankie.
- Alright.
My invention exchange this week,
these fully lined
leather sprinkler pants
that I like to call
lederhosen-hosen.
Now I can schottische
while watering my plants.
In my lederhosen-hosen.
(humming)
(laughing)
I just wanted to wear
lederhosen, okay?
It's a stupid
invention, I admit it!
I just wanna be Bavarian for
one brief shining moment.
Is that so wrong?
- Oh Frank, yes, it
is wrong, deeply wrong
but you've been under
a lot of stress lately.
Tell you what, we'll get
you an alp and a horn.
Would that make you feel better?
- Yes!
- Why don't you go on with
your invention exchange, Jim?
- It's Joel and if you'll
indulge me, your hinder-ness,
I'd like to turn over this
week's invention exchange
to our own Crow T. Robot.
- Thanks y'all.
The vulture, long associated
with pestilence and death,
is in reality a clean
and helpful bird
who is quite easy
to get along with
so to improve his
image, I invented Sarah,
the bobbing buzzards.
- Really?
- Yeah, based on the
water drinking bird,
this friendly carrion
eater cleans up roadkill
or table scraps.
- That's great, Crow.
- Kind of looks like you, Crow.
- I think you'll agree
there are few sights
in nature as beautiful
as a plump member
of the cathartidae family
pulling a sinewy string
of fetid meat off a weak
dead Thompson's gazelle.
There's a theme song.
Wanna hear it?
- Uh, sure, Crow.
♪ Bobbing buzzard,
caw, caw, caw ♪
diddily diddily deet ♪
(mumbling)
(horn blowing)
- Your movie this week, Joel,
(coughing) stars the--
- Ricola?
- Oh, thank you, Frank.
Would you just get back there?
Your experiment this week, Joel,
stars Sean Connery's
brother Neil
and they're more than
happy to tell you that.
It's called Operation Double 007
and now I have to
strangle Frank.
- Help!
♪ Bobbing buzzard,
caw, caw, caw ♪
- By Crow.
(shouting)
(buzzing)
(whirring)
(humming)
- [Tom] Stop.
Hey.
Assault on a queen.
- The Danny Bonaduce story.
(laughing)
(muffled singing)
- [Joel] Mutiny on the Betsy.
- Good thing they have
an espresso machine.
- [Tom] Get over here
and turn the music down.
- [Joel] Oh, like this?
(whistling)
All hands on me!
♪ He eats tuna
salad sandwiches ♪
Honey.
♪ I give him my love ♪
- Is there anything
this guy doesn't do?
- [Joel] Kid power!
- [Tom] I sailed to Tahiti
with an all girl crew
and all I got was
this wet t-shirt.
(laughing)
- Uh-oh.
You know when
there's four people
on a screenplay there's
gonna be trouble.
(muffled singing)
- [Joel] You know,
I'm suddenly hungry
for Cracker Jacks
and I don't know why.
♪ He sat on his glasses once ♪
- Sure would like to get
permission to come aboard.
♪ He likes to wear mittens ♪
♪ He's got a deviated septum ♪
♪ He's a real big
fat adult bird ♪
♪ He gets his
haircut on Tuesdays ♪
♪ He prefers stuffing
to potatoes ♪
♪ His favorite movie
is Turner and Hooch ♪
♪ Hurray for
(mumbling) clothes ♪
This guy can't possibly live up
to the song they
wrote about him.
Probably just an
accountant named Wallace.
- [Joel] So you're
saying you like this guy?
- [Tom] Oh no, please
don't hold back.
How do you really feel?
♪ He is the only one I
ever fell in love with ♪
(muffled singing)
- Women who sing too much.
- [Tom] And the men
they sing about.
- [Joel] Port of call, Sydney.
♪ The man for me ♪
♪ He is the man ♪
- [Tom] Now this
is one nutty navy.
- We do more hair and
makeup before breakfast
than most people do all day.
- [Joel] Hey, it's
the Old Spice guy.
- It is.
- [Tom] Must be one of
those airplanes I've
heard them talk
about so much lately.
- [Joel] Ah, Paul
William's lunchbox.
- [Crow] Stay there my friend.
- [Tom] No one else has a lunch
anywhere as good as mine.
- We now return
to Ship of Fools.
(mumbling)
♪ You taught me how
to doo doo doo ♪
- [Tom] Huh.
You know, if William
Conrad were there,
they could watch a
letter box version.
- If he wants to
change the channel,
does he get another woman?
Oh yuck, she's
(mumbling) his back.
- [Joel] Oops, wrong room.
- [Tom] Should I come back?
Yeah, I'll come back.
- Oh thank God, I thought we
were gonna see his naked butt.
- [Joel] Thank you sir,
I'll bill your room.
- [Tom] Hello, I'm Merv Griffin.
- [Joel] I was just gonna
press pause but nah.
- What's it like
being the TV, Cyndi?
- [Tom] Well it's better
than (mumbling) his back.
- Now showing on my back,
Morgan Stewart's coming home
at two, four, six, and eight.
- [Joel] Yes, may we help you?
- [Tom] When did I hire you?
- This is one great Motel Six.
- [Tom] Ah the life, huh?
- [Joel] Thank you
for touching me, sir.
That will keep me going
for the entire day.
- Eleanor, is this your robe?
- [Tom] They're on
the PMS Pinafore.
(beeping)
- Someone's on a pogo stick.
- [Tom] Huh?
What the?
- [All Three] Oh.
- [Joel] Uh, it's been
nearly two minutes
since anyone's fondled you, sir.
- [Tom] It's for you.
- Tell him I'm not here.
- [Tom] Hey Buck,
itty bitty bitty.
- [Joel] Now wait a minute,
how is it that he
gets color on his girl
but only black and
white on his TV?
- What's Moneypenny doing there?
Isn't that a
conflict of interest?
- [Joel] Oh that's nice.
They have a bar sign
up there for the pilot.
- [Tom] They have a
very loose dress code
at this business here.
- Tora!
Just the one.
- [Tom] I like planes.
- [Joel] Is this a cyst
on the back of your head?
- [Tom] Up yours.
Sit and spin.
(beeping)
- [Joel] Come in, Thunderbirds.
- [Tom] Johnny
Astro, real radar.
- Claude Rains pops the clutch
and tells the world
to eat his dust.
- [Joel] James
Brolin in The Car.
- Michael, I want all
episodes of Captain Niceburn.
- [Tom] Oh my God,
Herbie's gone bananas!
- This is Bob going in
my imminent death hole.
- [Joel] A Screen
Gems presentation.
- [Tom] The late Waldo Pepper.
(screaming)
- Thanks for the all
clear, Moneypenny.
- [Tom] Suddenly
she's a coffee table.
- [Joel] You know,
I love my torsos.
No.
- Uh-uh, uh-uh.
- [Tom] Please no.
(group retching)
- [Crow] I think I know
why Thunderball was a hit.
You never saw him
kiss anyone in it.
- Hurry!
- [Tom] This is Rita Braver
reporting to you live
from Krakatoa, east of Chava.
- [Joel] Here come the clowns!
(humming)
- There might be bees
burning in there.
I've gotta save 'em!
(sniffing)
- [Tom] Something smells good.
- [Joel] Hey, look what I found.
I think it's a guy!
- Well, he's Cajun now.
Better call Paul Perdone.
- [Tom] I'm gonna run in
the sprinkler, whoopee!
- [Joel] Well, you know
there's probably nothing
but bass jigs in there.
- Gilette foaming is so thick,
it can put out this fire.
- [Tom] Guys, I'm
gonna go start lunch.
I'll meet you back at the ranch.
Sandwiches again?
Okay, see you later.
- [Male] It's too
late, he's dead.
- Alright, help me
get him out of here.
Let's (mumbling).
(upbeat music)
- [Joel] Quick,
some lip blusher.
- [Tom] Oh, this game again.
- Thanks Roy, I
appreciate your help.
- [Joel] Now why is she
dressed like Barney Rubble?
- [Tom] Mustang Sally, you
better slow that Mustang down.
- Hello, Maya speaking.
Ward died in the explosion.
- Is that okay?
- I have the box with me, over.
- Fine.
Now let's get to work
on his girlfriend.
The Japanese.
- [Joel] Oh, and happy
secretaries week.
I bought you a gun.
♪ How will you make
it on your own ♪
- It's up to you now.
- Mm-hmm.
- This time, I want
the girl alive.
I've got a few
questions to ask her.
- Oh, and lose the Ringo hat.
(shouting)
- [Joel] Sir, you're
not wearing any pants.
- [Tom] The banks
of Circle Pines.
- New city ordinance,
all buildings
to be painted beige.
- [Joel] Get Christy Wong.
- [Tom] Oh, you see,
this is what happens
when you bob for french fries.
- Gentlemen, here we
have a practical example
of the theories I
have illustrated.
- [Joel] I suggest
we ox-ecute them.
- Two weeks ago, the
patient you see here,
Ms. Yachuko, sustained first
and second degree burns.
- [Tom] At my hands.
- On her face as
shown on the slides.
- I'm looking for Fang, ha ha!
- [Doctor] They called me
here from Edinburgh last week.
When I saw this
girl's condition--
- [Tom] I heaved.
- [Doctor] I decided
to operate immediately
before scar tissue
began to form.
I'm glad to be back here in time
to show you the results of
this operation personally.
- [Joel] It's great to be here.
Thanks for supporting
live surgery.
- [Doctor] Fantastic.
- Now Michael Jackson's
journey is complete.
- [Doctor] A miracle in plastic
surgery, don't you think?
- A miracle, yes.
- [Tom] Plastic surgery, eh.
- [Joel] Oh, she's turning
Japanese, I really think so.
- The results are due not only
to modern surgical technique
but also to an ancient
Tibetan process
defined as the hypnotic
process of total recall.
It differs from
the usual hypnosis
in that it allows us to operate
with the complete surrender
of the subconscious
and thus obtain the
patient's collaboration.
- Doctor.
(speaking in foreign language)
- He's asking when
the buffet starts.
- Dr. (mumbling) was asking me
if it would be possible
to make a demonstration
of hypnosis of total recall.
- [Tom] No.
- This experiment
requires the outlay
of a great deal of energy.
- Why don't you try it?
- [Joel] Why don't you bite me?
- No, no, not the young lady.
- [Tom] Her hat's too big.
- Excuse me, doctor.
I really thought that
I was just whispering.
- Actually, it's my fault.
I didn't hear you but I
am capable of lip reading.
I would say the young lady
is not an ideal subject
for this sort of thing.
- [Joel] 'Cause she's hot.
- She appears to have
unusual willpower.
I'm afraid it would
take too long.
- [Tom] I found that
out the hard way.
- However, we have Ms. Yachuko
with whom I have already
conducted experiments
of the same type and it
would simplify things
if Ms. Yachuko would agree.
- Thank you, Mr.
Connery's brother.
- [Doctor] Gentlemen, please.
- [Joel] Watch Neil rock.
- [Tom] Sleep!
- [Joel] Alright,
here's the church,
here's the steeple, open
the door and go to sleep-le.
- The Sixth Sense
with Gary Collins.
- [Tom] The powers
of Matthew Star.
- [Joel] You know, is Rick
Wakeman on the premises?
- [Tom] I would think so.
- Well, the cast of Jacques
Brel are on the scene.
- Now Ms. Yachuko has lost
direct contact with time.
- [Tom] She thinks she's
in Dresden during the war.
- Right up to the present
day is at our disposal.
It can be totally brought
back if we so desire
because every experience
she has lived through
has been registered
on her subconscious.
- [Joel] We're
from the yearbook.
- Greater precision
than the most highly
developed electronic brain.
- Let's pants her subconscious.
(chattering)
(growling)
- That'll be enough for now.
What are you doing,
leave her alone.
- [Joel] I have her til Tuesday!
- Well the Rodney King
verdict just came in.
- [Joel] Nancy
Sinatra's kicking ass.
- [Tom] Uh-oh, Lynn
(mumbling) fights back.
- Not exactly Jackie Chan is it?
- [Joel] Everybody
stop flipping.
- [Tom] I'm not
a hugger, please.
- You hurt me!
- [Joel] You know
I can read lips?
Did I tell you I
could read lips?
I'm reading lips right now.
- [Tom] Naughty little girl.
- Sam Donaldson!
- [Joel] Tales
from the Dark Side.
- [Tom] They need
coffee in there quick.
- It's Michael Caine, look out!
- [Joel] Well that
was easy, geez.
I'm already running
ahead of schedule.
- [Tom] I wonder
who that could, oh!
- [Maya] Get out, yes, hurry!
- [Male] Right!
- We just came to
beat everybody up.
We're leaving now, thanks.
- I hate to be interrupted
when I give a lecture.
♪ Old Judd Fry is dead ♪
- This man is dead.
- [Joel] No duh.
- Yes, unfortunately I
found myself distracted
so I used the
sublime (mumbling).
It's fatal.
- Don't tell me, doctor,
that there's anything
that would be able
to distract you.
- Oh yes, for instance,
when a charming girl
keeps gazing out of the window
while a brawl is going on.
It's your fault if
my jaw is broken.
- Oh I'm sorry, what can
I do to make it up to you?
- Paint my house.
- What do you suggest?
- Come on, you guys, let's go.
I've got an idea for
a really neat scenario
or a scene maybe.
(whirring)
- Joel's really gone off
the deep end this time.
- All I know is in
this outfit, I feel
like a total fem.
You know what, I don't
have a problem with it.
- You know, well I'd, uh ...
(dramatic music)
- Alright, time for
my daily back rub.
Who's going to do the honors?
- Joel, none of us
have working arms.
- I know.
(dramatic music)
- Hey Joel, what is that thing?
- It's all part of
my diabolical plan.
- But it's just a useless
prop that you built.
It's not even
connected to anything.
- I know.
(dramatic music)
(kissing)
- Joel, is there
any point to this?
I've got a lot of work to do.
Would you mind telling us
what this is all about?
That's it.
- I've had enough.
- Joel, you're
ruining it for me.
- I know.
- It appears to me--
- [Crow] Really
fun sketch, Joel.
- [Joel] I know.
- Wait until the judge
gets his verdict.
What else can you do?
Don't forget, we have a
corpse to deal with here.
- [Joel] A cawpse?
- And Ms. Yachuko's
disappeared too.
Sorry, doctor.
- [Joel] I'm talking
to Fudgie the Whale.
- Until the
investigation is over.
- How long will that take?
- We're moving as fast as we can
but please don't set
foot outside the limits
of Monte Carlo until you
get the okay from us.
- But I have to go back
to Columbia University.
I have some operations
that are waiting.
I can't remain
here indefinitely.
- The former Ms.
Moneypenny, sir.
- [Male] Your highness.
- There's your man, commander.
- [Tom] I hope you'll
be very happy together.
- [Joel] He's hardly Sean, I
realize, but he comes cheap.
- The Osterman weekend.
- Ms. Yachuko was right.
- [Tom] That's an ugly beard.
- You can see the resemblance.
- [Joel] To John Sexton.
- Think so?
I'm not so sure of that really.
I don't think he's
quite so good looking.
- Oh yeah?
- Why don't we shave the
beard off just to make sure.
- [Joel] Just peel it off.
- The beard is mine.
I'm attached to it.
I want it to remain right there.
And furthermore, I'd like to
know what's going on here.
- I'm cunning.
(mumbling) counter espionage
for Western Europe.
- [Tom] (mumbling)
the elven king.
- This is Ms.
Maxwell, my assistant.
You were the brother
of our top agent.
- [Tom] Mike Lovitz.
- So I think we can trust you.
(humming)
- [Joel] The flirting nun.
- [Tom] You got it.
(chuckling)
- Swiss steak for
lunch, lucky guy.
- [Tom] I'd like to
make a confession.
I think you're hot.
(laughing)
- [Joel] You know,
Dave Barry's not funny.
- I should have used (mumbling).
- [Joel] Turn your
head, you're fine.
- [Male] Drop that knife.
- [Tom] Do you mind,
we're playing war games?
- [Joel] Does he have a
fur ball or something?
- [Male] Drop it I said.
(Clacking)
- [Joel] I am the walrus,
coo coo ca (grunting).
- [Tom] I think I had
her in eighth grade.
- [Joel] Now time
for his catheter.
- She's a flibbertijibbet,
will o' the wisp, clown.
- [Tom] I want this
problem called Maria
taken care of permanently.
- [Joel] Sister Mary Mayhem.
- Father forgive me
for I have murdered.
- [Tom] Yea, though I
walk through the shadow
of the valley of death, oh.
(springing)
- Make me happy, how'd I do?
- [Joel] She is good.
- [Tom] Maybe there is a
role for women in the church.
Sisters are doing
it for themselves.
- [Joel] Sin and
the art of archery.
(humming)
- This handy hostage packs
into a compact nine by 14 case.
Hard case also available.
- [Joel] She's making
a human burrito.
- [Tom] Make it snappy, sister.
I got other pick ups, come on.
- I'm married to
the Lord, you know.
- [Joel] Oh boy, I'd kill for
a jump cut right about now.
- Oh Lord, please let
my work reflect thee
in thine eyes.
- [Tom] The few, the
proud, the opus dei.
(muffled singing)
- [Joel] Is this a
documentary on how
to do this, whatever this is?
- She's a stunt nun, you know.
I saw her get interviewed
on the Sci-Fi channel.
- [Tom] Sheesh, send
her to an outward bound
and this is the result.
- [Joel] Now this
is when you sit back
and watch it all come together.
♪ Let Hertz put you
in the ambulance ♪
- [Tom] (mumbling) 182.
- [Joel] We'll have
her back tomorrow.
- Human cleaners.
We'll clean your
humans overnight.
- [Tom] Dodge vans,
more room, same ride.
- [Joel] Now let's
review the steps
on how to run a
hostage down a rope.
- Could we stop at
a Baskin Robbins?
- [Tom] Oh, they're repo clergy.
- [Male] Dr. Connery, would
you look at that photo?
It was in Ms. Yachuko's bag.
She said you know him.
- It's Ward Jones.
He was planning to marry her.
- [Joel] Then I showed up.
- I met him when he took
my course in hypnosis.
The one I gave in Japan.
A very capable chap.
- [Tom] Thinks
he's a chicken now.
- I saw Jones
killed this morning.
- Ward's been killed?
- By the same people who
tried to kidnap Yachuko.
- [Tom] The shriners.
- He's back in our hands.
Ward had important information
he wanted to sell us.
Unfortunately, he was killed
before he got it to us.
- Actually, Ward asked
us to protect Yachuko
because he'd given her
some secret information
and he was afraid she
might be in danger.
Now she denies this absolutely.
- Is this a Barnaby
Jones wrap up?
- And I'm inclined to think
she's telling the truth.
- But we can't find any
explanation to this business.
- Then I'll explain it to you.
- [Joel] What happened
was just this--
- Ward learned a
special yogi technique,
quite complicated
but very effective.
Briefly, it's very
possible to communicate--
- I'm not getting any of this.
- A state of hypnosis
of total recall.
The subject himself
doesn't know he knows
but he would be able
to repeat verbatim
if he was again hypnotized
to the same extent.
- But do you mean
that's how Ward Jones--
- Precisely.
- [Joel] You're welcome.
- It's clear Ward used Yachuko
as a human electronic brain,
a sort of impregnable safe
to keep his secrets in.
- Cuckoo, cuckoo.
- Safe that you know
how to open, of course.
- I'm sorry but
I can't help you.
I'll be too busy for
the next few days.
- Why, doctor?
All you have to do is to
walk around Monte Carlo
for the next few
days until the police
decide to let you go.
- [Tom] Which I doubt.
- And if I help you
out, you'll get me out.
Is that what you mean?
- Freedom always has a
price tag attached to it.
- [Tom] Oh, I guess we're early.
- [Joel] I hate that suit.
- He's had it.
- Poor guy.
- I've never seen a
knife like that before.
- [Tom] One side's a
scaler and the other--
- Let's see if
there are any clues.
- He died listening to Rush.
- [Joel] 2112.
- Put it in a
projector right away.
He may have had
time to get a photo.
(mumbling)
- [Tom] The pocket sized
machine that goes ping.
- [Joel] This is the
GAF murder view master
- Sister Chuck Yeager.
(laughing)
- [Tom] That flower actually
takes pretty good pictures.
- Bloody Krayendorf.
- Then it's THANATOS.
- Thanatos?
- One of the most powerful
gangs in the world.
- [Joel] They beat me
up when I was a kid.
- So they're mixed
up in this then.
- What kind of a hospital
are you running here?
- This is beginning to
look pretty serious.
- [Tom] We'd better
bring Sean in.
- [Joel] A spy movie
is starting to sag
and Ed Asner is there.
- Looks like the Bigfoot
video, same stride.
- [Tom] The Alps are
beautiful but dark.
- [Joel] From the street
this place looks really small
but from the back it's huge.
- [Tom] Wow.
- Good god I'm ugly.
Scared my own children
out of the nursery today.
- [Tom] I've decided, we're
ordering from Schlotzsky's.
Standing in front
of a (mumbling).
- [Joel] We're ordering
lunch, what do you want?
- Excuse me.
I'm three minutes late.
- That's okay.
We're a pretty loose group.
- [Tom] Nice hat.
- [Joel] He's
three minutes late.
- [Male] Gentlemen.
- Start your engines.
- Operation Blackmail.
(mumbling)
is drawing to a close.
- [Joel] It's been a lot
of fun for all of us.
- To carry it
through successfully
so that we may control
the world's gold reserves
requires unfaltering discipline.
- [Crow] Splunge for me sir.
- [Male] Represent
the gold reserves
of the six wealthiest
nations of the world
and your respective duties are--
- [Joel] Wait for it.
- To lure these six powers--
- [Crow] Oo hoo!
- Into a trap.
You realize, gentlemen--
- [Tom] I'm binding.
- That this is the greatest
financial undertaking
in history.
(upbeat music)
- We've traced
the Japanese girl.
She's in Malaga.
- [Tom] Nice beanie.
- If you mean you want me
to go with you to Spain,
I can't accept the invitation.
- But it's a quick
trip and pleasant.
- Sorry but I won't
play any spy games.
If you let them snatch
Yachuko from under your nose,
that's your fault.
- Take off the Tom O'Shanter.
- Wait a minute, you
can't back out now.
I have a cable from
the minister of health.
- [Tom] The minister of hell?
- Putting you under
my orders for a month.
- [Joel] Let's see, I
like you, do you like me?
Minister of health.
- Operation double O girl scout.
(laughing)
I can't read.
- That's an order, doctor.
- [Tom] Well kiss my
white Scottish arse.
- Do I have time to change?
- Certainly.
I'll be waiting in the
bar for you so hurry.
You have a plane to catch.
- Waiting in the bah.
- [Tom] Waiting in de bar.
- [Joel] I'm gonna
get you, I will.
- Just hanging out in the yard.
- Have you lost anything?
- Yes.
- [Tom] The top
third of my dress.
- The button came off.
- A very thoughtful bow.
- She has handles.
- Thank you, it's
very kind of you.
- Any reward?
- [Joel] Yeah, can I get
your brother's autograph?
- Come on, doctor,
you've a plane to catch.
- One second, there's a
reward I must collect.
- Just remember your
name is Neil Connery.
Now get in the plane.
- You have to leave
the account open.
Max is waiting for
you at the airport.
- [Tom] Double O
double entendre.
- I hope I see you again.
- I think she's neat.
♪ Well shake it up baby, now ♪
- [Joel] Man, it sounds
like the British invasion's
waiting for a flight out.
- [Tom] And when you
deplane in Malaga,
you'll be greeted
by Manfred Mann.
- They should be here.
- Do I have enough time
to beat up the band?
- [Joel] They call
it the mercy beat.
In five minutes, you'll
be screaming for mercy.
Thank you.
- They're playing
a penguin song.
(quacking)
- [Tom] Hey, it's Moneypenny,
pull over, it's Moneypenny.
- [Male] Thanks a lot.
- [Joel] That's okay.
- Will you marry me?
- The telegram just came and
I left my dear little bride,
Consuela, and all
of the other guests
in front of the church.
As you see, Max, I'm
getting married today.
- [Tom] Caught Moneypenny.
- Where is Yachuko?
- Watch me dance.
- [Joel] Oh, not
another bowl losing.
- At first sight I
took you for an azalea.
What have you lost now?
- My necklace.
Oh, it's so sweet to
see you again, doctor.
- Same to you.
- Hey, it's Bernie
from room 222.
- Dr. Connery, you're
so very kind as usual.
- [Neil] My pleasure,
I'm very kind by nature.
- I'll remember that.
- [Tom] Hair by Jim Henson.
- [Neil] Why don't you
remember it tonight?
- [Joel] Hey, who's
your favorite clown?
- [Both] Bozo!
- [Joel] Hey, that's me!
- Come on, doctor.
- Sorry.
- My husband Fang, ha ha!
- [Tom] This Friday on Streets.
- [Joel] This must
be the traditional
call to gambling in Monte Carlo.
- Go out and get
some air, fatso.
(shouting)
- [Joel] It's a little
drafty in the winter
but you can really stretch out.
- Yachuko!
- Hey, this isn't how
we left her with you!
- [Tom] He who
withdraws the blade
is right wise born
king of England.
- Who's been here?
- [Joel] Some guy with a knife.
- Poor girl.
She didn't have anything
to do with this.
- But this is not Yachuko.
- [Joel] There was no Yachuko.
- She's a double, I tell you.
A good double but that's all.
- Solid double down the line.
- Are you sure?
- Positive, I know
her pretty well.
I've operated on her face.
- That means that
they used her as bait
to keep us off the track.
- [Joel] Are you gonna
marry me or what?
- If you wanna find the real
Yachuko and still alive,
I've a feeling you'd
better get moving fast.
- Ew.
- Well, what have
you lost this time?
- Oh, I've lost my lighter.
- [Tom] And my dignity.
- [Neil] Do you ever walk
upright like other people?
- [Joel] Pantsuits from the
Mary Tyler Moore collection.
- [Neil] If I were a
lighter, where would I go?
- Oh there it is.
- Excuse me.
- [Neil] There it is
indeed, there you are.
- [Tom] You have a
nip, er, cigarette?
- Not in front of
Sir Walter Raleigh!
- [Joel] Flint, Flint!
- My reward.
- [Tom] That's it?
- You've got gorgeous
eyes, you know.
- Oh, do you really like them?
- Very much.
- Can I have one?
- [Joel] Oh Neil, this isn't
right, I don't think that--
- Ew, she's got
(mumbling) on her face.
- Secret Agent John Ivan Palmer.
- And now you will
do whatever I want
and you will tell me
everything I want to know.
- [Joel] Let's talk hockey.
- And you must obey me.
Who sent you here?
Thanatos?
- Yes.
- [Tom] Lip sync.
- Who was their cheat?
- Edward Clap?
- Nobody knows.
♪ The trouble I've seen ♪
- What are they planning?
- I don't know.
- Do you know where
they've hidden Yachuko?
- Yes.
In (mumbling) villa near Malaga.
Just past the
crossroad of Marbella.
- By a Tom Thumb.
- And is it heavily guarded?
- It's surrounded by
a high tension fence
and there's a machine gun too.
- Whether that's
heavily guarded,
I suppose it depends on your
definition of heavily guarded.
- [Tom] Can I get your
brother's autograph?
- You know, you've got
beautiful eyes too.
- [Joel] No, you've
got beautiful eyes.
- No, you've got beautiful eyes.
- [Tom] And then of
course, oh my God.
- Well, well, well.
It looks like nobody in your
family is a rank amateur.
- Let me get rearranged here.
- To think this was supposed
to be my wedding night.
- I'm sorry to break up
your little tete a tete
but we've received
information that Yachuko
is being held prisoner
outside Grenada.
- That's funny, the
opposite direction.
- Who told you that?
- She told me.
♪ She told me ♪
No, let her go or we
might ruin everything.
- [Tom] Wow, what a cigarette!
- Maximum tanning.
- [Joel] The
president's analyst.
(whimpering)
- You know, some people
just can't wake up
no matter how many
alarms they set.
- Stop now.
- [Tom] Looks like you
got an extra game there.
- [Joel] Sacre bleu.
Sacre bleu, huh?
- Oh yeah, sacre bleu.
- [Joel] Let's go lift, man.
- [Tom] Looking good.
- It's alright, you can rest.
Calm down.
- [Tom] Mother Grimm
with her hair down.
- They've made you
suffer, haven't they?
How can they make such a
pretty girl suffer like that?
- I'm asking myself
the same thing.
- You mustn't be afraid of me.
- [Joel] Here, have
some new Miller Clear.
- [Female] We women understand
each other, don't we?
Here.
- [Tom] Water, it's
what's for dinner.
- Drink.
It'll do you good.
- Bread will be out shortly.
I'll let you look at the menu.
- What do you want from me?
I told you I don't
know anything.
I really don't know anything.
- [Female] Why are
you so obstinate?
- [Joel] I get it
from my father.
- We know that Ward
confided something to you.
- It's not true,
no it's not true!
It's not true!
How many times do I have to
tell you I don't know anything?
How can I convince you?
- [Female] If you talk,
I shall reward you
in a way you can't even imagine.
- [Tom] I'll leave.
- You'll live with me.
- [Tom] Do you smoke?
- Like a princess.
- But I don't know anything.
I swear it!
(screaming)
- [Joel] Welcome to noogie hell.
- [Tom] Hello Vincent!
- Hello Theo!
- [Tom] Where is Vincent?
- I am here, Theo.
- [Tom] I feel like Gauguin
in freaking Tahiti here.
- [Joel] Man, I'm
really hot, are you hot?
Geez I'm hot.
- (mumbling) you're my
knight in shining armor.
- [Joel] Hey Greg, heard
it through the grapevine.
(laughing)
- [Female] Is that darn
thing going to work?
- [Tom] Operation
double double O Hee-Haw.
- [Neil] If my
calculations are correct,
the short circuit
should cause a return
of current capable of
blowing up the turret
with the ammunition.
- [Joel] Anyway, I got
Lulu backing me up.
- Hooty hoo, hooty hoo!
- This is your local
utility company
reminding you to
call before you arc.
(exploding)
- [Joel] Fran Liebowitz!
- [Tom] Follow zee everybody.
(upbeat music)
- Hi.
Welcome to a segment we like
to call the Sean and Neil
Show, Parallel Lives.
- In which we look at
and contrast the careers
of Sean Connery and his
brother Neil Connery.
Let's start off
with today's movie.
- Yeah, this line
represents Sean's life.
This one represents Neil's life.
I'll give you an example.
Sean's acting
talent is discovered
at an early age
and leads to a long
and lucrative film career.
- While Neil's talent
for selling light bulbs
over the phone is
discovered leading
to a long life of menial jobs
and aimless drifting.
- Well up here is when Sean
gets his first million
dollar royalty check
for the James Bond series.
- While Neil gets his first
65 dollar unemployment check
after being laid off
from the cheese factory.
- Here Sean is declared
sexiest man alive
by People Magazine.
- While Neil is declared
the stinky cat man
in room 4B by the other
tenants in his SRO hotel.
- Here, Sean calls
the most powerful
and influential
people in Hollywood
and is put through immediately.
- While Neil calls
Pizza Hut and is told
that they won't deliver to him
because of bounced checks.
- Here Sean is quoted as
saying during the making
of the Man Who Would Be King,
I had creative differences
with Director John Houston.
- While Neil is quoted
as saying my manager
at the Happy Chef won't
let me off for weekends.
What a dink, man.
- Here Sean goes to Spago's
and is seated immediately.
- While Neil's hot
plate malfunctioned
and burns down his
shabby furnished room.
- So Joel, what about
that point on the graph
where Sean's line actually
goes lower than Neil's?
- Oh, well that was the point
where Sean agreed to do
Highlander Two, The Quickening
and ironically, that's when
Neil had to comfort Sean.
- You know, we should remind
the nice folks out there
that this is merely artistic
speculation on our part
of Neil Connery's life.
For all we know, he's leading
a prosperous happy existence
on a farm in Scotland
with his beautiful wife
and adoring children.
- That's right,
Tom, and no matter
what's gone wrong with his life,
Neil can always
look in the mirror
and say to himself, well,
at least I didn't do Zardoz.
- Right, and so, Neil,
wherever you are,
we would all just like to say--
- [Group] Oh, we've
got movie sign!
(whirring)
- [Tom] That went well.
Don't you think that went well?
- [Joel] Yes, it did.
- [Tom] I thought
that went well.
- [Male] Don't move!
- [Tom] Okay move.
- [Male] Let the girl go!
- If you love your
hostage, let her go.
- Drop that knife.
Drop it.
- [Tom] Julia Samples
and Linda Hunt
in a deadly game
of cat and mouse.
- Watch out!
- [Joel] She's so calm.
Her roommate just got
shot and she's so calm.
- [Tom] The Sod
Squad, Julie, Pig, Eb.
- Let's go.
- Ah, the calla lilies
are raining hot lead.
- Go on, I'll cover you!
- [Joel] (mumbling) coming
through, (mumbling).
- [Tom] (mumbling) is the
shakiest gun in the west.
(laughing)
- Cover me, Norman.
- [Tom] The Rocketeer!
- Oh, it's the only way
he can talk to women.
- [Neil] I am Ward.
- [Tom] You are June.
- Ward.
I told you something
about THANATOS.
Remember what I told
you about THANATOS?
- Yes, THANATOS.
♪ Thanatos ♪
- Atomic nucleus.
- Good, what else
did I tell you?
- Go 22, Paris six.
Two words that was.
- Two words, bite me.
- [Tom] Judy Karn?
- [Joel] Wait a minute, she
looks like (mumbling) now.
- She's a Tony girl.
- Go on, what
happens in Tetouan.
- [Tom] Watch Bond
take short hand.
- Work in Tetouan.
- [Joel] Uh, slow down.
- (mumbling) in Tetouan.
- [Joel] Just a second.
- The blind?
Try again.
(gun firing)
- Oh, now come on!
- [Tom] Lady, you are due back
on the Space 1999 set.
- [Joel] Joan Jett just
walks in and she takes over.
- Sorry.
- It's nothing.
- I'd hoped to get
here before she talked.
- [Tom] Couldn't get a cab.
- Perhaps I could
have saved you.
(gun firing)
- [Joel] Was I
supposed to do that?
- [Tom] I'm a picking.
- [Joel] And I'm a kill it.
- Nice going, you
just killed Sacagawea.
- What did you get
out of Yachuko.
- Nothing much.
Mostly in a sort of code.
It must be deciphered.
- [Joel] As if I'm
not busy enough.
- She spoke also of Tetouan.
Something strange, the
blinded eye in Tetouan.
- What else did she say to you?
- [Tom] She wanted my
brother's autograph.
- It seems that
THANATOS isn't joking.
They're planning to
steal an atomic nucleus.
- Atomic nucleus?
- [Joel] Oh, that's
what I use on the corn.
- Why it's not possible.
- North Dakota before
the apocalypse.
(humming)
- [Joel] Wow.
- Consider Northern
Illinois University.
- [Female] The atomic nucleus.
And only a jeep for an escort.
- [Joel] Hey, here
come the Brides,
there's a road show.
- Why Matthew, it's a
herd of Ms. Kitty's.
- [Tom] They can hit
60 in three spurts.
- [Joel] Tailhook
takes it on the road.
- [Tom] A few good men
meet a few naughty women.
Ooh la la.
- It's a man's life in
the new modern army.
- [Joel] Our Partridge
Family van broke down.
- [Tom] She looks
like an oil fire.
(mumbling)
(firing)
- It's the puza dart band, no!
- [Tom] They're just gonna
tag 'em and check 'em
for parasites.
♪ Gamera, Gamera ♪
- [Joel] Oh see, gays in
the military right there.
- Hey gals, when
does the sex start.
♪ Then Felina goodbye ♪
- [Female] They'll
sleep til morning now.
- [Joel] Just what are these
women trying to liberate?
- [Female] Alright girls,
get out of those clothes.
- Where angels go,
trouble follows.
- [Tom] She could be a
candidate for Big Bird.
Definitely.
- [Joel] Bury my
dress at wounded knee.
- [Female] Now let's get
to work on the truck.
- We gotta hit Le Pew's place.
- [Tom] So the composer's
whistling at them.
(whistling)
- Am I tripping, Joel?
♪ Jesus loves me ♪
- [Joel] And Las Vegas was born.
You stop it.
♪ The Bible tells me so ♪
- [Joel] Stop it.
- [Tom] Sorry.
- [Joel] They keep
busy, don't they?
- You wanna help
out here, Susan?
- [Tom] Tonight, the dirty dozen
meets Blansky's Beauties.
- Seems like the
seductress pole cat
had other things on her mind.
- [Female] Well let's go.
- [Joel] They're
setting up a Goony Golf.
- Alright, drive on.
- Terrorists were
more fun back then.
- [Tom] This is even better
than Mission Impossible
when they take a street in LA
and make it look like Belgium.
- It's Big Al Hurt and
Pete Found marching us all
out of this seat, thank you.
- [Tom] The hell was that?
- Gentlemen.
- I prefer blondes.
- With his usual brilliance
and imagination--
- [Joel] Carrot Top.
- Beta has secured the
atomic nucleus we need.
- [Tom] Yes, (mumbling)
atomic nucleus (mumbling).
- We are in position to
continue with our plans.
Beta will now explain to you
the experiments our technicians
have been carrying out--
- Dressed as showgirls.
- [Male] Over the
past few weeks.
- [Joel] Thanks for the
marvelous introduction, Irv,
I'll take it from here.
- Gentlemen, I shall
start by saying these
are all just small
scale experiments.
- [Group] These are all just
small scale experiments.
- But now, with this powerful
material at our disposal,
we are at last able to
generate ultra high frequencies
and to direct the magnetic wave
to at least a
third of the globe.
All metals will be
instantly effected.
- (mumbling) will be
bred and slaughtered.
- [Male] Will fuse solidly.
- [Tom] Chilitos
will be half off.
- Dynamos will cease.
(mumbling)
Ships, planes, guns,
tanks, armaments.
Everything mechanical--
- Must be sold.
- A useless lump of metal.
- [Tom] Oh, and forks.
From high atop the
Top Copy Palace
in downtown Istanbul, it's
Fred Waring and his orchestra.
- [Joel] That may drop later.
- [Tom] The remaining
monkey brains
have been reduced
to a dollar 99.
- [Joel] Nice digs, huh, Susan?
- Where's the guy
with the pickled eggs?
- Take it to the red room.
- [Joel] One more time.
- [Tom] They look like
Electra Woman and Dyna Girl.
(laughing)
- Other guests are coming.
- [Group] From Europe.
- [Tom] Rubenstein and Sammy
Cahn walking arm in arm.
- Doctor.
How nice to see you again.
- Thank you.
- One second.
- [Joel] You're dressed
as a space angel, why?
- How lucky Maya
asked you to come.
I was going to get
in touch with you
to arrange a meeting.
- Could you feel
this bump on my head?
- Oh of course,
the returning game.
I had no idea you were
so interested in archery.
- I'm not.
It's your services as a plastic
surgeon I'm interested in.
- [Crow] Oo hoo!
- Why, would you like to
have your features changed?
- Me?
Oh no, I'm quite
satisfied with my face
and with my nose also.
- Although I do weather
vane in high winds.
- It's for a friend.
He wants to become the
exact double of another man.
- [Tom] Bob Eubanks.
- But for the time
being there's no need
for you to understand
and of course--
- [Crow] You don't.
- You can state your own price.
- [Tom] Welch's?
- For me, it's not
a matter of money.
It's primarily a
matter of principle.
- Although I'm a
little low today.
Do you have 10 bucks?
- To an agreement, you'll see.
We'll have time
to talk about it.
- [Joel] I lost my pockets.
- [Tom] Bobby Gentry, so
good to see you again.
I don't know who invited him.
- Will you excuse
me for a minute?
I won't be long.
- [Joel] I've been
advised I look ridiculous.
- I'm sure with so many
beautiful girls around,
you won't get bored.
- [Tom] Oh no, you're right.
Course, women are
just all over me.
I mean, I got no problem
if you know what I mean.
- [Joel] Rocky mountain oysters?
- Thank you.
No thank you.
- [Crow] Do you have any
snackish type foods here?
Summer sausage,
toothpicks maybe.
Those little mints.
Ron.
- [Tom] David.
- Well?
What have you done?
- [Male] Not very much.
It's difficult.
They're all afraid of Alpha.
- Idiots.
- Maybe they're right.
After all, Alpha is powerful.
- [Tom] We've got a good bench.
- [Beta] Come in.
- There's a message
from the yacht.
It's very urgent.
- Hi.
- [Joel] See here, it says
take off that ridiculous getup
and it's signed yacht.
- It's from Alpha.
- [Tom] He's having a good time.
- He set the date.
He wants me to join
him immediately.
- We're to be married.
- What timing.
- It'll be the last time
he gives me an order.
I'll destroy him and I'll
be the head of THANATOS.
- It is very, very risky.
- Not for me.
- What about the girls?
Then they'll be
dangerous witnesses.
- As soon as the
operation is over,
the yacht will blow up.
- [Tom] Remember,
folks, he can read lips.
He is reading lips right now.
- With the girls aboard?
- Yes.
- Yes!
- I am too?
- It's inevitable.
- [Tom] I German
the yellow frog.
What bozo the piano chive?
I used to be good at this.
- There must be no witnesses.
Only you will share my secret.-
- You know that
you can trust me.
- Now let's go inside and
see if we can convince them.
- [Joel] And
remember to have fun.
- Marla Maples.
- Doctor.
♪ My eyes have seen the ♪
- May I divert you
from your meditation?
- A coincidence, I was
just thinking of you.
- I'm flattered.
- Looks like her tomato
asp got away from her.
- Maya.
- [Joel] There's a
big bug on your head.
- In serious danger.
- Are you threatening me?
- No, certainly
not but I have just
overheard a conversation
between your Mr. Thayer.
Yes, I've seen few villas
as beautiful as this one.
It's quite splendid.
- [Tom] Act natural, your
lips might be pucked.
- Oh Donald.
- Senor Mendoza.
- [Joel] Jessye Norman
wants her kaftan back.
- You're not going, are you?
I was hoping to play a hand
of chemin de fer with you.
- I don't gamble, Mr. Thayer.
I only bet on winning horses.
- That's why you should stay.
- [Tom] Melvin Laird's
getting cheesed.
- [Beta] I have an important
announcement to make.
- [Joel] I'm Rue McClanahan.
- I thought you had
the voting majority.
- [Beta] As far
as I'm concerned,
this meeting never happened.
Let's drop it and leave
things as they are.
- I shouldn't advise that.
- [Tom] Oh, I'm
sorry, (mumbling).
- I want to know whether you
are with me or with Alpha.
- Or with child.
- I warn you, be
careful how you answer.
- [Tom] The Beatles!
- You could put yourselves
in a dangerous spot.
- Under my kaftan.
- It's a lot more
dangerous to listen to you.
- [Tom] Ooh.
- In a few days,
Alpha will be dead.
- [Joel] Criswell predicts!
(humming)
- But no one will
know except us.
Within hours, I'll have
an exact double for Alpha.
- Neat huh?
- Everything will go on
as if nothing happened.
- [Joel] Nothing has happened.
- But with this difference--
- Your hair can have
more body and shine.
- The new Alpha will be my man.
♪ Oh my man I love him so ♪
- It's going to blow up
soon, maybe even tomorrow,
with you on board.
- [Joel] You're kinda
hard to dance with.
- You read too many
novels by Fleming.
- Jerry Fleming, Ian's brother.
- I assure you it's true.
Your life is in great danger.
- [Tom] I'm that bad a dancer.
(laughing)
Seriously.
- I'll keep everything
under control somehow.
- With my control
top panty hose.
But seriously.
- If my information is right,
you'll be indebted to me.
- [Joel] He sounds
like Hercules.
- Good.
- Anyway.
- Why does Mr. Thayer
hire only blind people
in his rug factory?
- [Tom] Wait, I know this one.
- Hi Largo.
- I don't know, I've
never been in there.
Only blind people are
allowed to go inside.
- [Joel] And I'm blonde.
But seriously, I--
- Excuse me.
- I have to go talk to
an interesting person.
- [Joel] She seems nice enough.
- Should have had her bring
me back some three bean salad.
(mumbling)
- [Tom] Das Bloat.
- [Joel] I should
get me one of those.
- It's Red October.
Hi Sean.
- [Joel] I could have
gotten a ride on that.
I didn't want to.
- [Tom] We have installed
a screen door, sir.
- How do you get this
thing out of reverse?
- [Joel] This man
could win 5000 dollars!
(speaking in foreign language)
- Michael Donahue.
- [Group] Hoo ha, hoo ha!
Hoo ha!
- [Tom] Oh brother.
- To sea or land?
- [Tom] I hope he can
read braille lips.
- You're new here.
(humming)
- [Joel] And they say a
Lou Reed shall guide them.
- Casting call for
Name of the Rose.
- [Tom] It's the
boys in the hoods.
(laughing)
- You know, I bet Dolphin Temp
has a hard time filling
these positions.
- [Tom] Bruno, Bruno!
- [Joel] Alright you
win, they're all blind.
- [Tom] Dick Enberg here!
- Hold on to each other by
the shoulder and come with me.
- Well it felt like shoulder.
- [Tom] So any of you
sure play a mean pinball?
- [Joel] Wait a
minute, the blind
leading the blind
leading the blind leading
the blind leading the blind.
- [Tom] Oh yeah, I'm
blind, yeah, blind.
- Listen all of you.
- [Joel] And you shall hear.
- Here you will weave rugs.
Don't worry.
It's a simple easy job.
You will get your food and
your family will get your pay.
- [Tom] There is a Coke
machine in the break room.
- Each one of you will
be placed at the loom
and will begin
with an easy task.
With a little goodwill,
you will learn quickly
and now get to work.
- Let's start with a
hot pad holder first.
- [Joel] Wait a minute, he's
infiltrated a quilting bee.
- [Tom] Goodwill Industries,
now it can be told.
- [Joel] Somebody
heard him looking.
(upbeat music)
- Pretty good.
Good enough for the state fair.
- [Tom] What's this?
The blind weaving the blind.
Wall to wall trouble
in Carpet Land, USA.
- [Joel] You know, ironically
Connery wears a rug.
(laughing)
- [Tom] That's very clever.
- Who is the sign for?
- [Tom] That must be where they
make the nuclear powered rugs.
- Shut the door,
I do believe I am
developing pictures
of rugs in here.
- [Joel] Hot L Baltimore.
Hot L Baltimore,
Hot L Baltimore.
- [Tom] Would you please
stop tapping like that?
- [Joel] You know, a buffet
would never work in this place.
- Are you Hank?
- [Tom] No.
- You smell like Hank.
(kissing)
This is like soap wood
only in a rug factory.
- [Tom] Silkworm.
- [Joel] You got some
marmalade on your hand.
- You're working with
radioactive material.
It will kill you.
- What is it that
you mean by that?
- [Tom] Sometimes I think
you want me to fail.
- You are working with
radioactive materials.
Do you understand?
- Yeah well I get paid
two dollars more an hour.
- It will kill you.
- They're trying to murder us.
That is why we have the sores!
We must go!
- [Tom] Neil's a skilled
rabble rouser isn't he?
(yelling)
Guys, that's not the
door, that's the core.
- I'm staying, I need the money!
- [Tom] It's gonna
take you, the police,
the fire department
and the national guard
to get me out of here.
- Hey, this is kind of fun.
- [Joel] This must be
five o'clock on a Friday.
You want it when?
- [Tom] Quit tussling me,
can't you tell I am fragile?
- Now everybody be sure to
sign Vicky's birthday card
before you leave.
She won't be here on Monday.
- [Joel] Looks like
casual day backfired.
(speaking in foreign language)
- [Beta] Alright, let him go.
- [Tom] Gee, I was
just on the road
to Damascus and
whammo, look at me.
- Is he wearing
a braille jacket?
- [Joel] He's pretty good, huh?
- Bad touch.
- Your Arabic is quite good.
Part of it dates from
the time of the crusades.
Dr. Connery.
- [Joel] Oh, I could
never fool you.
Give me a hug.
- [Tom] Is it my scene now?
(mumbling) at nine now, huh?
- Ladies and gentlemen,
Maynard Ferguson
in the centennial
senior high school gym!
- [Joel] Bobby
Joe, get back here.
- You're an extraordinary
man, doctor.
- [Tom] I know.
- Let me show you my (mumbling).
- Imaginative and resourceful.
- [Joel] Nice
sense of humor too.
- It's too bad you prefer to
play on the opposing team.
- [Neil] Too bad from
your point of view.
- [Joel] Ooh!
- Yes.
But it is my point
of view that counts.
- I know you are but what am I.
- [Beta] If you'd done me
the small favor I asked--
- [Tom] You'd be in
marketing by now.
- [Beta] There would have been--
- [Joel] More chip dip.
- No such
complications as these.
Now you'll have
to operate anyway
under less favorable
circumstances.
You understand?
- [Neil] Well what
else can I do?
- Again, oh.
- [Tom] It's a new car!
- [Joel] Neat, where's the bach?
- Here is your patient, doctor.
- Doctor, patient,
patient, doctor.
- Everything's ready for you.
I want to be generous.
- [Joel] So here's a quarter.
- In return for your services--
- [Tom] You get to rub my tummy.
- Your life.
♪ You've come a long way, baby ♪
♪ To get where
you got to today ♪
- [Tom] Can I borrow
your miniskirt
for the party on the Lido deck?
- Girls.
I've got to warn them.
I have just learned
that we're going
to have to fight for our lives.
Thayer's decided to
blow up the yacht
with all of us aboard.
Come on.
- That's a bad thing, right?
- If it stops, so will yours.
- [Tom] Look, I just
came in for a haircut.
Really just a little
off the sides.
- [Joel] Okay.
How are we today, good, good.
You're looking good.
How's that little
prostate problem?
- Alright, you can go.
- Can we have the
night canopy please?
- [Joel] You know, I
think that operating room
clashes with the couch.
- Just relax.
You're tired.
You want to rest.
That's right, relax.
You have nothing to fear.
- [Tom] I'm going to
enter your nostril now.
- [Joel] Steve Austin.
- [Neil] That's right.
- [Tom] That's it, yes, yes.
- Couple of tucks, he
could be Roy Fennis.
- [Neil] Deep, deep sleep.
- [Tom] Where was your chest
on the night of the 23rd?
- [Joel] Oh, he
(mumbling) that speaker
from a drive-in.
- As soon as Connery has
completed the operation--
- [Tom] You'll get new sweaters.
- I want him eliminated.
- Ew!
Hi.
- Hello.
- [Joel] Tony Basil.
- [Tom] Ooh!
- The lust boat.
- [Tom] Boy, women have really
broken the glass ceiling
in this movie.
- Yeah, but there's a guy
looking up through it.
- [Joel] Women,
can't live with 'em,
can't live without 'em.
- It's closing time at Hooters.
(whistling)
- [Joel] He deserved that.
- Still, it was worth it, ugh!
- [Tom] Ole!
- Now you will follow
my instructions.
- [Tom] Sit, stay.
- You won't have
a moment of peace
til it's all finished.
- [Joel] Can you even dye
my eyes to match my doll?
- [Tom] Any old time.
I see here that you
haven't been flossing.
- [Joel] Now, how do
you like your martini?
Shaken or stirred?
- I'm taking the
president's nose.
- Now go.
(yelling)
- [Joel] The anesthetic
wore off, ah!
- [Tom] I love you, damn it!
- [Beta] Have you gone mad?
- Police squad in color!
- [Joel] Take this,
John Entwistle!
- [Tom] He did, too.
- Oh Danny, let's
settle this in court.
- [Joel] Watch out
for the model ship!
- [Tom] An actual donnybrook
in easy spirit pumps.
- [Joel] It's the
wackiest ship in the navy!
- When up with people goes bad.
- [Joel] That was a
real Capezio kick.
- [Tom] Did someone say fight?
- Enter the chiropractor.
- [Joel] Chuck Taylor's.
Stop the scene right now!
- That violates some rules.
- [Tom] I woke up, you
weren't there, I hate that.
- Watch out for the model!
- [Tom] The hell?
- Right into a
Bob Fosse routine.
- [Joel] Ms.
Partridge, look out!
- [Tom] No, this is
a one seater, Homer.
- It's hullaballoo or.
Where the action
is or hootenanny.
- [Joel] Happening 68.
- Yeah.
- [Joel] If Sam Peckinpaw
directed The Boatniks.
He's wearing a Linus shirt.
- It's no reason to hit him.
- [Tom] There's just no end
to these little blue guys.
- That's a cute top,
Cyndi, where'd you get it?
- [Tom] Not now.
- Sorry.
- [Tom] Boy, that is one figure
hugging turtleneck there.
- [Joel] Oh poopy.
Licorice?
Oh.
- Oh great, now
the boat's sinking.
- [Tom] I finally
got used to that.
- [Joel] Wait a minute,
he's becoming part
of his own entertainment center.
- Scuse me, pardon
me, coming through.
Oh scuse me, oh broken out, hi.
Oh, oh, scuse me, pardon me.
I'm sorry, hi Betsy.
Scuse me, pardon me.
- [Joel] And as Falco
shows his true colors
of yellow and flees the Calypso.
- [Tom] And as we left
the clam flowage that day.
- [Joel] Stop that.
(gun firing)
- Let's see you hypnotize
him from here, Mr. Cool.
- He's heading there.
- We can't worry
about that right now.
We've got to find
THANATOS headquarters.
The radioactive rugs
were made at the factory.
Where were they sent?
- I really never knew that
but once I heard something
about a place near Munich.
- [Group] Munich!
(shouting)
(whirring)
- No, no, no.
- Come on, just let me
try to hypnotize you.
Crow, sit.
(clucking)
- You can't make me, you can't
make me, you can't make me!
- Oh what the--
- Ah Joel.
So sorry to interrupt
your little skit
but Frank would
like to do a number.
I was a little hard on him
during the invention exchange.
So here's our own TV's Frank
accompanying himself
on the accordion
with the haunting
beer barrel polka.
Humor him, okay?
- And a one, two, three, four.
(mysterious music)
- Ah, that's rather nice.
Not really a polka.
More of a march.
Good.
Very familiar.
- Here are the Mr. Pibbs
that you ordered sir.
- Oh thank you, just
put them on the, you!
What the, didn't you--
- Mr. Pibb?
I specifically
ordered a Diet Squirt.
- I'm so sorry, gentlemen.
I'll make it right.
- No, no, no, no.
Frank, have the Mr. Pibb.
You can have the
Mr. Pibb this time.
- No, my doctor says
I can't have Mr. Pibb.
- Frank, I'm your doctor
and I say have the Mr. Pibb.
- Master wanted you
to have these coupons
for our veggie feast.
He wanted you to have them
but I'm giving them to you.
- Thank you very
much, I thank you.
- Yes, have a nice day.
- I was, thank you, goodbye.
- Oh, may I use your bathroom?
(upbeat music)
(clicking)
- There, on the left.
Alright, let's land.
(mumbling) indicates
that's the spot.
- [Tom] High on a hill
there's a lonely goat herd
so you might wanna take an
alternate route this afternoon.
- [Joel] This place is
crawling with Chatham's.
- Ping!
- [Joel] Maybe you should
land before you get out.
Oh.
- [Tom] Honey,
you got your keys?
Your keys!
- [Joel] She's nude!
- Let's take a
look in that shed.
- [Tom] This place.
- This feels great.
Pleather is really something.
- I'm beginning the countdown.
- [Male] Begin countdown.
- [Joel] Knock it off, Trevor.
- 120 seconds.
- [Male] Warning signal.
It's Connery.
He's found the secret entrance.
- [Beta] Such a curious man.
I'll satisfy his curiosity.
Let him in.
- [Tom] Double 007 is on.
- [Joel] Turn it off.
- [Male] 114.
- Sir, someone's doing
a drunk test outside.
- [Male] 112, 111.
110.
- [Joel] I'm gonna shut you
down til about 20, okay, Trevor?
Trevor!
- [Male] Connery's
now in the tunnel.
- Oh, now it's the Outer Limits.
I'm not going in the tunnel.
Oh, I am in the tunnel.
- [Tom] Boy, it reeks down here.
- [Joel] Hey, put
that thing away.
- [Male] Stop right there!
- She's not the only smooth one.
- [Tom] That's for stealing
my naugahyde couch.
(groaning)
- Maya, you'd
better call London.
- Alternate vibrators.
- [Male] Alternate
vibrators inserted.
- Hey, you can't say that.
- [Tom] So how come everyone's
got Count Basie following them?
- [Joel] Heidi is grown up.
(group groaning)
- [Joel] The backstab, stab.
- [Tom] Thank you, Ron Popeil.
- What would my brother do?
- [Joel] That must be
the fine arts building.
- [Tom] So I guess nobody's
gonna notice the guy
in the tan suede ranch
jacket, are they?
- No.
- [Joel] Sun Ra's band!
- Leave me alone!
- [Tom] Air Wolf
meets Dr. Zhivago.
- [Joel] Should we be
moving or something?
- [Tom] Big old helicopter.
- Everybody, when that lady
gets off the helicopter,
check out her pants.
(mumbling)
- [Tom] Wait, can I
get, oh, for crying out,
where's the valet?
Forget it.
She's smooth, she's
really smooth.
- Hello, Ms. Pants,
I mean, oh shoot.
- [Tom] Give me an
espresso, please!
- It's terribly urgent.
- [Male] London in England?
How do you expect to do that?
- A telephone, please help me!
It's a matter of life and death.
- [Male] You can try.
I don't know if
you'll get through.
- [Joel] Oh, there's Waldo.
- [Male] 31.
- 30 seconds.
- [Male] Magnetic intensity
at concentration level.
- [Tom] Thank you,
Charles Aznavour.
- [Male] Yes.
Magnetic wave ready to function.
- [Joel] It's just an elaborate
clothes dryer, that's all.
- Hello London.
Extension 142.
I want to speak with Commander
Cunningham immediately.
It's terribly urgent.
Never mind who I am, hurry.
- Five.
- Bottles of beer on the wall.
- Four.
- Three.
Two.
- A castle on the hill?
- [Tom] A lonely goat herd?
- But how far from Munich?
- One.
♪ Singular sensation ♪
- The headquarters
are 20 miles from--
- [Joel] Wahappa.
- Hello, hello?
- [Joel] I don't know why
you say goodbye, I say hello.
- We've been cut off.
- Well, I'm not
calling her back.
- I'm wondering--
- [Tom] What do
the simple folk do?
- Whatever will this
do to my underwire bra?
- [Joel] That does it,
now where did I park?
- Gotta admit it.
- [Tom] Boy, you know,
those slacks hurt me.
(humming)
- [Tom] McCloud.
- So, Mr. Bond's brother.
- I'm happy to have
you as my guest again.
I'll show you how
the operation works
on our anti-magnetic equipment.
- [Joel] Oh, you get A&E.
- Don't you think?
And that's the last
favor I can do you.
I only allowed you to live
because I wanted you
to witness my success.
I've got what I wanted
without your help.
- [Joel] Nah.
- Take him away.
- [Tom] I think I'm supposed
to have some snappy
comeback here but, ah.
- [Joel] No,
further, keep going.
Don't look at me like that.
- Suddenly it's the
Brothers frigging Karamazov.
- The magnetic wave
has blocked it.
- Aren't you a
champion archer too?
- No, sorry about that.
I'm a pretty good fighter though
and I guess that
could be useful too.
- [Tom] Can it?
♪ Their cars broke ♪
♪ Their horses will poop
on the parking lot ♪
- Look, they outlawed night.
- [Joel] You guys
look really stupid
in plastic pants, plastic pants.
- [Tom] (mumbling)
is down there.
Oh boy, another
stare down with Neil.
- [Joel] Go mental.
- Rick, what's wrong with you?
There's my Phillips screwdriver.
♪ Oh we oh, we oh ♪
- [Tom] I wish they'd stop
pretending this is exciting.
- [Joel] Hey, that looks
just like a U2 video.
♪ Under a blood red sky ♪
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Come on you
guys, it's Neil Connery.
You should be able to get him.
- [Joel] Oh my pants, my pants.
- Come on.
- [Tom] Oh, what a
time for a fire drill.
Ha, see how that alligator
skin hat helps you now, huh?
- Come on girls,
they hurt Buddy!
- [Joel] Mommy!
- [Tom] They shot Jolson!
(shouting)
Wait, that's not,
give me it, I got it.
- Where are you going?
- I'm trying to
blow up the tower.
- Hold it, take this.
- [Joel] My grandma
gave it to me.
- It's an anti-magnetic--
- Thing!
- Explosive.
- Can I set the dial?
- Sure you can.
- Good.
- We'll cover you.
- [Tom] Okay, we'll
meet you there!
- [Joel] It's the
Elmer Fudd brigade.
Oh, fell right on it.
Oh, again.
- [Tom] Come on!
(chattering)
Sierra.
(mumbling)
- Trade you!
(firing)
- [Joel] Blue archer
must be on this case.
The archers.
- [Tom] Geez, everybody
gets a turn here, huh?
- [Joel] Encore, mommy!
Mr. Belvedere!
- [Tom] Better park
the hard drive here.
(mumbling)
- This is your last
chance for a witty remark.
- At your own game, doctor.
- [Joel] It's a perfect
set up for a witty remark.
Come on!
I mean.
- [Tom] Come on, doctor.
It's no good if
you don't retort.
Could be anything.
Can be about my nose or
my stupid alligator suit.
Anything!
- Hey, that's not fair.
- [Joel] Geez you're
soggy in this suit.
- Okay, here's the stunt batch.
- [Joel] Ow.
You know, guys, I think
this is about more
than just magnetizing.
- [Tom] This goes much deeper.
Stunt largo, look guys.
- Yep.
Hey, somebody punched
the foley guy.
- [Tom] Okay, okay,
take back everything
you ever said about me.
- [Joel] Oh man am I moist.
Tony Fields was
never this moist.
- [Tom] Haha, prepare to meet
Kali's brother near hell.
- Bow fight at the OK Corral.
- [Joel] I'm gonna do it!
(laughing)
- [Tom] Oh.
- [Joel] You know, he's
gonna need a vinyl patch kit.
- [Tom] Oh, are these
guys still at it?
Good gravy.
- [Joel] They're
beating up LaBeau.
(humming)
- You know, for some
reason I liked the fight
on the boat better.
- [Tom] Me too.
- [Joel] Uh, hey Vern.
- [Tom] A uvula.
Hey everybody, there's a
party going down at the--
- We've got to get out
before the tower blows up!
- Well.
- [Tom] Oh, and I forgot
to tell you earlier
that there's a
tower that's going
to blow up in this soon.
- Oh, I just got
it, that's the tower
that's gonna blow up.
- [Tom] That they
didn't tell us about.
(exploding)
- [Joel] Are we gonna die?
We're really not that far away.
- [Tom] The Brigadoon
compound exploded today.
(mumbling) escaped unharmed.
Unfortunately Bonnie
Jean has died.
- Kinda like watching
Bonanza in reverse.
- [Tom] That must be the
thunder ball I heard them
talk about so much, maybe.
(firing)
- [Joel] Hey relax,
we won, you hot head.
(laughing)
- Okay, Connery, okay.
You were fantastic.
You even made my best
agents look like beginners.
- Oh, I shouldn't
think so, commander.
I was lucky, that's all.
- No, you're too modest.
You should have seen your
brother's face, doctor.
When he heard of it.
- [Tom] Settle back with a
smooth Canadian (mumbling).
- If you happen to
have a few days free,
I was thinking I'd
be happy to have you
back in the reserves
with the rank of major.
- If I wasn't so
placid right now.
- You would?
- [Tom] Church steeple.
Sleep-le.
- [Joel] Boy George?
- Major.
- Nelson.
- What was I saying?
- That you have to return
to London immediately.
Isn't that right, commander?
- [Joel] It works
on my brain too.
- Yes, of course.
I must return immediately.
- [Joel] I'm a famous
lounge singer, I am.
I'm Ms. Norman Maine.
- This is the part my
brother told me about.
- [Tom] Yes, I should
take my own life, yes.
- Angel of death.
High powered rifle.
Emulated crossfire.
- [Joel] We're having fun
at his expense, it's fun.
- [Neil] Ready girls, let's go.
- He probably hypnotized
her into liking him.
- [Joel] Yeah, I
should think that life
would lose a lot
of its zip if you
had ultimate power over
everyone, you know.
- [Tom] Sean Connery's
brother won't
be back again in anything.
(laughing)
♪ He loves me ♪
(Whirring)
(grunting)
- Oh what the?
How do you suppose
this happened?
- We're stuck to the wall.
- Ah criminy.
- Holy cats.
- Wow.
- Are you guys
stuck to the wall?
- Yeah.
- We're immobilized.
- We're stuck!
- Oh, I bet I know
whose idea this was.
Sirs, was this your idea, huh?
- Hm?
Why Joel, I.
You got me.
(laughing)
No lo contendre.
I saw the movie, remembered
I had my old magnetizer.
These things are great.
You gotta admit
it's pretty funny.
I'm stuck to the wall.
- It's no use, Joel.
It ain't gonna work.
I'm stuck.
- Now what?
Quick, get me
rocket number nine!
Very funny, sirs, but I'll
have you know that
you're probably
interrupting intercontinental
telecommunications.
- Yeah!
- Oh, wouldn't wanna do that!
Don't worry, we'll
demagnetize you guys later.
(laughing)
(speaking in German)
How about a Ricola now, Ernst?
Until next time,
Joel, auf wiedersehen.
(toilet flushing)
- [Torgo] Thank you.
(mysterious music)